Hilpert, Elmer E. Arbitration Papers 5493
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Elmer E. Hilpert Arbitration Papers
1943-1975
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Hilpert, Elmer E.
5493
91 cubic feet
91 linear ft.
Case files, proceedings, transcripts.
Files include correspondence, briefs, transcripts, exhibits, awards. Many of the case files in this collection contain a substantial amount of documentation.
2299577
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 30, 1986
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 14, 2019
Biographical / Historical
Professor Elmer Hilpert (1905-1975) received his JD degree from Case Western Reserve University in 1936 and a JSD degree from Yale University in 1939. He was an instructor in political science at the University of Minnesota and was appointed as assistant professor of law at Case Western Reserve University in 1936. He moved to Louisiana State University in 1937 and was appointed associate professor of law at Case Western Reserve University in 1938. In 1939, Hilpert became associate professor of law at Washington University. Hilpert had an active career as a mediator and arbitrator and was the impartial referee for the Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Company and the United Automobile Workers and for the Glass Containers Manufacturing Institute and the Glass Bottle Blowers Association for many years. Arbitrator and professor of law.
Scope and Contents
Includes arbitration cases involving Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Company vs. United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America and Allis-Chalmers vs. International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America.
Includes cases arbitrated by Hilpert between Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Company and the following unions on the following issues: United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America on issues of rates of pay, job classifications, discipline, dismissal, job assignment, managerial prerogatives, seniority, and grievance procedure (1955); International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America on issues of seniority, recall after layoff, demotion, discipline, authority of arbitrator, job classification, vacations, layoffs, managerial prerogatives, rates of pay, overtime pay, termination of employment, job assignment, holiday pay, incentive pay, reduction in workforce, shift differentials, recall, failure to report, vacation pay, transfers, union representation, dismissal, lunch periods, layoff for disciplinary reasons, promotion, bargaining unit work, reduction in work force, insurance eligibility, plant shutdown, contracting out, downtime, union jurisdiction, probationary employees, grievance procedure, and computation of overtime pay (1955-1961).
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Arbitration, Industrial -- United States -- Cases; Industrial arbitrators; Absenteeism -- Arbitration, Industrial -- United States; Alcohol abuse -- Arbitration, Industrial -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- Agricultural machine industry -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- Aircraft industry -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- Automobile industry -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- Brewing industry -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- Cement industries -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- Chemical industry -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- Container industry -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- Distilling industries -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- Drug trade -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- Electronic industries -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- Flour and feed trade -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- Food industry -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- Foundries -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- Furniture industry -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- Glass manufacture -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- Grocery trade -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- Lead industry -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- Meat industry -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- Merchant marine -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- Metal-workers -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- Paper industry -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- Petroleum industry -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- Public utilities -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- Retail trade -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- Rubber industry -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- Shoe industry -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- Steel industry -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- Transportation -- United States; Contracting out -- Arbitration, Industrial -- United States; Employee fringe benefits -- Arbitration, Industrial -- United States; Employee rights -- Arbitration, Industrial -- United States; Employees, Dismissal of -- Arbitration, Industrial -- United States; Employees, Training of -- Arbitration, Industrial -- United States; Grievance procedures -- Arbitration, Industrial -- United States; Hours of labor -- Arbitration, Industrial -- United States; Industrial safety -- Arbitration, Industrial -- United States; Job descriptions -- Arbitration, Industrial -- United States; Job vacancies -- Arbitration, Industrial -- United States; Labor discipline -- Arbitration, Industrial -- United States; Labor productivity -- Arbitration, Industrial -- United States; Layoffs -- Arbitration, Industrial -- United States; Management rights -- Arbitration, Industrial -- United States; Misconduct -- Arbitration, Industrial -- United States; Vacations, Employee -- Law and legislation -- United States; Plant shutdowns -- Arbitration, Industrial -- United States; Position classification -- Arbitration, Industrial -- United States; Promotions -- Arbitration, Industrial -- United States; Seniority, Employee -- Law and legislation -- United States; Technological innovations -- Arbitration, Industrial -- United States; Labor unions -- Recognition -- United States; Union security -- Law and legislation -- United States; Wages -- Arbitration, Industrial -- United States; Wages -- Pharmaceutical industry employees -- United States; Wages -- Grocery trade -- United States; Work assignments -- Arbitration, Industrial -- United States; Work assignments -- Arbitration, Industrial -- United States; Employee rules -- United States; Working conditions -- Arbitration, Industrial -- United States; Hilpert, Elmer Ernest, 1905-; A.E. Staley Manufacturing Company; Allied Chemical Corporation; Allied Materials Corporation; Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Company; Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America; American Bakery and Confectionery Workers' International Union; American Car and Foundry Company; American Federation of Technical Engineers; American Oil Company; Armco Steel Corporation; Armor Elevator Company; Arvin Industries; Borden Company; Borg-Warner Corporation; Brockway Glass Company; Brotherhood Railway Carmen of America; Brown Shoe Company; Century Electric Company; Cerro de Pasco Corporation; Communications Workers of America; Container Corporation of America; Dow Chemical Company; Emerson Electric (Firm); Federal Barge Lines, Inc.; Federation of Glass, Ceramic and Silica Sand Workers of America; Firestone Tire and Rubber Company; General Electric Company; General Steel Castings Corporation; Glass Bottle Blowers Association of the United States and Canada; Glass Containers Corporation; Goodyear Tire and Rubber Company; Granite City Steel Company; Great Atlantic & Pacific Tea Company; Grinnell Company; Gulf States Paper Corporation (U.S.); H.K. Porter Company; Hagar Hinge Company; Henry Vogt Machine Company; Independent Oil Workers Union; Independent Union of Chemical Plant Workers; Indian Head Company; International Association of Machinists; International Brotherhood of Blacksmiths, Drop Forgers, and Helpers; International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers; International Brotherhood of Firemen and Oilers; International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite, and Paper Mill Workers; International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America; International Chemical Workers Union; International Organization of Masters, Mates, and Pilots; International Shoe Company; International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers; International Union of Operating Engineers; International Union of United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, Soft Drink, and Distillery Workers of America; International Union, Allied Industrial Workers of America; International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America; Krey Packing Company; Kroger Company; Laclede Gas Company; Laclede Steel Company; Lockheed Aircraft Corporation; Magnavox Company; Mallinckrodt Chemical Works (Saint Louis, Mo.); McDonnell Douglas Corporation; Midwest Rubber Reclaiming Company; Missouri Portland Cement Company; Mobil Oil Corporation; Monsanto Chemical Works; Motor Carriers Council of St. Louis; Nat Carling Breweries Inc.; National Distillers and Chemical Corporation; Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Workers International Union; Paint Makers and Warehousemen; Ralston Purina Company; Retail Clerks International Association; Retail Clerks' International Protective Association; Retail Clerks International Union; Schlueter Manufacturing Company; Servus Rubber Company; Shampaine Company; Sperry Rand Corporation; St. Joseph Lead Company; St. Louis Soft Drink Bottlers Association; St. Louis Steel Casting, Inc.; Texaco, Inc.; Textile Workers Union of America; Union Carbide Corporation; United Brick and Clay Workers of America; United Cement, Lime and Gypsum Workers International Union; United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America; United Papermakers and Paperworkers; United Paperworkers International Union; United Plant Guard Workers of America; United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America; United Shoe Workers of America; United States Plywood-Champion Papers Inc.; United Steelworkers of America; Utility Workers Organization Committee; Utility Workers Union of America; Valley Steel Products Company; Valspar Corporation; W.T. Grant (Firm); Wagner Castings Company; Wagner Electric Corporation; Warehouse and Distribution Workers Union; Western Electric Company; Westinghouse Electric Corporation; Saint Louis County (Mo.). St. Louis County Water Company
2299577
- AMBAC Industries vs. Int'l. Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers (IUE), Local 794., 1970 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  2/20/70. Issue: classification of job - new job
- ARO, Inc. vs. Int'l. Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW), Local 2113, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  2/18/67. Issue: classification of jobs - posting
- ARO, Inc. vs. Int'l. Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW), Local 2113, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  March 1967. No award.
- Acme Markets, Inc.vs.Int'l. Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen & Helpers of America (IBT), Local l69, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  1/12/71. Issue: discipline - discharge
- Acme Paper Co.vs.IBT, Local 688, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  7/14/66. Issue: assignment of job - assignment of work outside unit
- Air Products & Chemists Inc.vs. UnitedSteelworkers of America (USA), Local 6063, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  8/24/65. Issue: hiring - temporary employees
- Air Reduction Co.vs.Int'l. Union, United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America (UAW), Local 523, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  3/16/68. Issue: contracting out
- Air Reduction Co. vs. Oil, Chemical & Atomic Workers Int'l. Union (OCAW), Local 3-556, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  9/9/66. Issue: contracting out
- AirTex Products, Inc.vs.UAW, Local 543, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  7/17, 18/58. Issue:insurance coverage
- AirTex Products, Inc.vs.UAW, Local 543, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  9/14/58. Issue: layoff
- AirTex Products, Inc.vs.UAW, Local 543, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  9/9/58. Issue:termination - seniority
- AirTex Products, Inc.vs.UAW, Local 543, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  7/17, 18/58.Issue: layoff - seniority
- AirTex Prod.Inc.- General file (Box 1, Folder 13)
  info re above 4 cases
- Airtherm Co.vs. USA, Local 2795, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  12/6/54. Issue: alcoholism - drinking prior to reporting
- Airtherm Co.vs. USA, Local 2795, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  8/6/64. Issue: rates of pay - shift differentials
- Alabama Power Co. vs. IBEW, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  9/20/68. No award
- Alabama Power Co. vs. IBEW, System Council U-l9, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  9/21/69. No award
- Aladdin Industries vs. USA, Local 4802, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  7/24/73. Issue: strikes - discipline
- Albers Construction Co. vs. Laborer's Int'l. Union of North America (LIUNA), Local 42, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  1/12/74. Issue: discharge - insubordination - failure to obey orders
- Alladin Plastics of Tennessee, Inc. vs. Plastics and Novelty Workers Union, AFL-CIO, Local 351, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  9/4/72. Issue: seniority - right to a job
- Allen Industries, Inc. vs. Textile Workers Union of America (TWUA), AFL-CIO, Local l374, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  6/5/58. Issue: contract interpretation, Premimum pay
- Allgire Towing Co. vs. Int'l. Brotherhood of Longshoremen, AFL-CIO, Local l652, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  8/23/57. Issue: lay-off - contract interpretation
- Allied Chemical Corp., General Chemical Division vs. OCAW, AFL-CIO, Local 7-669, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  5/15/60. Issue: rates of pay - temporary assignment; grievance - prior settlement
- Allied Chemical Corp., General Chemical Division vs. OCAW, AFL-CIO, Local 7-669, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  10/23/60. Issue: seniority - reduction in force
- Allied Chemical Corp., Solvay Process Div. vs. OCAW, Local 3-586, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  11/10/66. Issue: suspension.
- Allied Chemical Corp., Solvay Process Div. vs. OCAW, Local 3-586, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  Issue: promotions - return to former job
- Allied Chemical Corp., Union Texas Petroleum Div. vs. Omaha Metal Trades Council, AFL-CIO, and its constituent Laborers Int'l. Union, Local 1140, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  10/29/73. Issue: contracting out - bargaining unit work
- Allied Materials Corp. vs. OCAW, Local 5-283, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  8/7/64. Issue: authority of arbitrator, discipline - discharge
- Allied Materials Corp. vs. OCAW, Local 5-283, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  10/24/68. Issue: vacancies - temporary
- Allied Mills, Inc. vs. Allied Industrial Workers of America (AIW), AFL-CIO, Local 898, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  2/21/64. Issue: arbitrability -timeliness; discipline - layoff
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Cedar Rapids, Iowa vs. United Electrical, Radio & Machine Workers of America (UE), Local 116F-UE, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  2/1/55. Issue: rates of pay - classification of jobs
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Cedar Rapids, Iowa vs. UE, Local 116F-UE., 1955 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  2/10/55. Issue: discipline - discharge
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Cedar Rapids, Iowa vs. UE, Local 116F-UE., 1955 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  2/1/55. Issue: classification of jobs - change in work assignments
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Cedar Rapids, Iowa vs. UE, Local 116F-UE., 1955 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  2/2/55. Issue: assignment of jobs - supervisors
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Cedar Rapids, Iowa vs. UE, Local 116F-UE., 1955 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  2/3/55. Issue: transfers - seniority
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Cedar Rapids, Iowa vs. UE, Local 116F-UE., 1955 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  2/3/55. Issue: assignment of jobs - seniority
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Cedar Rapids, Iowa vs. UE, Local 116F-UE., 1955 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  2/2/55. Issue: grievance procedure
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Cedar Rapids, Iowa vs. UE, Local 116F-UE., 1955 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  3/26/55. Issue: arbitration procedure - appeal and review of award
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Cedar Rapids, Iowa vs. UAW, Local 1316, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  6/22/57. Issue: seniority - date of eligibility
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Cedar Rapids, Iowa vs. UAW, Local 1316, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  6/18/57. Issue: recall - failure to recall
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Cedar Rapids, Iowa vs. UAW, Local 1316, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  1/17/57. Withdrawn
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Cedar Rapids, Iowa vs. UAW, Local 1316, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Cedar Rapids, Iowa vs. UAW, Local 1316, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  1/17/57. Issue: overtime.
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Cedar Rapids, Iowa vs. UAW, Local 1316, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Cedar Rapids, Iowa vs. UAW, Local 1316, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Cedar Rapids, Iowa vs. UAW, Local 1316, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Cedar Rapids, Iowa vs. UAW, Local 1316, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Cedar Rapids, Iowa vs. UAW, Local l3l6, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Cedar Rapids, Iowa vs. UAW, Local l3l6, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  6/19/57. Issue: demotions - discipline; seniority; arbitrability; authority of arbitrator
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Cedar Rapids, Iowa vs. UAW, Local l3l6, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  6/20/57. Issue: classification of jobs
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Cedar Rapids, Iowa vs. UAW, Local l3l6, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  1/17/57. Issue: classification of jobs
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Cedar Rapids, Iowa vs. UAW, Local l3l10, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  8/9/57. Issue: transfer -seniority
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Gadsden, Alabama vs. UAW, Local 487, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  9/19/54. Issue: discipline - discharge
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Gadsden, Alabama vs. UAW, Local 487, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  8/30/54. Issue: seniority - super seniority.
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Gadsden, Alabama vs. UAW, Local 487, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  3/10/55. Issue: vacations - layoff
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Gadsden, Alabama vs. UAW, Local 487, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  6/26/56. Issue: vacations - layoff
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Gadsden, Alabama vs. UAW, Local 487, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  6/29/55. Issue: seniority - layoff
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Gadsden, Alabama vs. UAW, Local 487, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  7/2/55. Issue: seniority - layoff
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Gadsden, Alabama vs. UAW, Local 487, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  5/8/61. Issue: discipline - layoff as disc
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Gadsden, Alabama vs. UAW, Local 487, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  5/20/61. Issue: discipline - layoff
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Gadsden, Alabama vs. UAW, Local 487, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  5/18/61. Issue: supervisors & foremen - inventory taking
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Gadsden, Alabama vs. UAW, Local 487, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  6/15/61. Issue: classification of jobs - transfers between classifications
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Gadsden, Alabama vs. UAW, Local 487, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  6/15/61. Issue: seniority
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Gadsden, Alabama vs. UAW, Local 487, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  8/30/62. Issue: rates of pay
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Gadsden, Alabama vs. UAW, Local 487, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  11/18/62. Issue: rates of pay
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Gadsden, Alabama vs. UAW, Local 487, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  11/21/62. Issue: discipline - layoff
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Gadsden, Alabama vs. UAW, Local 487, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  11/24/62. Issue: discipline - layoff
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Gadsden, Alabama vs. UAW, Local 487, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  11/27/62. Issue: layoff
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Independence Works vs. UAW, Local 487, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  2/6/67. Issue: overtime pay
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Independence Works vs. UAW, Local 1958, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  2/4/67. Issue: termination of employment - disability
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Independence Works vs. UAW, Local 1958, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  2/5/67. Issue: overtime pay
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Independence Works vs. UAW, Local 1958, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  3/16/67. Issue: rates of pay - cost time pay
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Independence Works vs. UAW, Local 1958, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  2/25/67. Issue: rates of pay - overtime
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Independence Works vs. UAW, Local 1958, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  2/23/67. Issue: call in -availability
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Independence Works vs. UAW, Local 1958, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  9/16/66. Issue: rates of pay - overtime, assignment of jobs
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Independence Works vs. UAW, Local 1958, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  2/8/67. Issue: holiday pay
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Independence Works vs. UAW, Local 1958, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  3/12/67. Issue: holiday pay - intervening employment
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Independence Works vs. UAW, Local 1958, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  3/6/67. Issue: shift transfers - seniority
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., LaCrosse, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 40l, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  9/25/54. Issue: union shop
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., LaCrosse, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 40l, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  9/28/54. Issue: discipline - layoff - negligence and carelessness
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., LaCrosse, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 40l, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  5/20/55. Issue: layoff - seniority
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., LaCrosse, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 40l, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  2/15/56. Issue: layoff - seniority
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., LaCrosse, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 40l, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  10/19/56. Issue: layoff - seniority
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., LaCrosse, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 40l, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  4/19/61. Issue: overtime
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., LaCrosse, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 40l, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  4/1/61. Issue: supervisors - bargaining unit work
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., LaCrosse, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 40l, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  4/3/61. Issue: layoff - seniority
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., LaCrosse, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 40l, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  4/19/61. Issue: overtime, assignment of
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., LaCrosse, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 40l, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  5/5/61. Issue: reduction in force - seniority
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., LaCrosse, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 401, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  7/9/54. Issue: rates of pay - incentive pay
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., LaCrosse, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 401, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  4/30/62. Issue: layoff - vacation pay
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., LaCrosse, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 401, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  11/23/61. Issue: classification of jobs - rates of pay
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., LaCrosse, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 401, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  12/l/61. Issue: rates of pay - transfers
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., LaCrosse, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 401, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  12/13/61. Issue: recall - seniority
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., LaPorte, Indiana vs. UAW, Local 1319, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 5)